Hello Hello friend welcome to Market
Studies I am your friend Kapil
Rastogi and now we will talk about ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited.
ICICI Lombard March
21 result in a weekly we will
share the result and technical and current news and related to it and first of all let us take
that ICICI Lombard General
Insurance if you start in 2017 at
2,000 you saw like all other
shares, after timely appointment and all the
ups and downs the share is above 1423, it is
not just a small thing, you can see it
depending on the road view at this time,
its March festival results have come
and we will move towards those research,
March 21 result is in front of you, a
rapid growth of 10%
is visible if you look at less hair and share 08 2014
accused 06 operating profit which is in its
place operating profit, in this video if we
talk about it then profit comparison
chart Shyam Shyam  Turn it off, okay, it is increasing.
Why did the operating profit fall and why did the net profit
rise by 348? Behind that, a word income, a big other
income was added. So, this is an overview of the results of these,
you can see that the GPS is increasing.
Fixed point 2050
was near 13.20. Beat 7.6, 10.3 and 10.7. If we
look at the city of ICICI Lombard above the place chat, then
what is the police relation. Now let's
talk about it. The rule that you are
seeing above it is its two-and-a-half-and-a-
half moving average and it
works for you there above, it has come from there and even
before this you can see that it had
supported once above the Ladla movie average
and you got to see a very good big jump.
If we talk about some time back, then
it was seen working with its 2.0 movie average day moving
average.
Set some time and sure, if you see it
works for six months, from 1339 to  And
1200 was subscribing and
we try to understand about it, we are
looking at the stock right now above its current position, so this is 1417 and which
level does this form, now we
try to understand this technically very carefully, so if we look
technically, why did this stock take
support on March 1st above this particular price
and after this, if we look, on
December 31st, above this level,
you were seen taking support above the issue price,
why above this point, on August 10, 2002, it was seen
pressing resistance, so
this is
working as both an important growth levels and support levels
for the stock,
that at present, when it gives
you clothing on its side after making profit, then the
first resistance level that you will see,
this first resistance level is
around 1454 Udayan more rupees, you will
see the first system inside this, the
resistance is 15000  15000 is
seen being formed, after that you should
subscribe here because if you
see on this, then from 9th December
onwards till March, it tested this level many times, that is the
price level, but it could
not take the picture there and
Shatrughan appeared to you in the lower area, so
if this stock goes upwards, then
which levels were formed, a level of Rs 1456 was
formed, a level around Rs 1528 was formed and
after that you can see a big boom in it
and then it can cross its feet height
level of 1621,
if this stock is seen coming down, then the
first point which is its
level around 3008 in 80,
you will see, which is seen forming its 200mb
and after that, if this stock goes down, then
you can see it coming above Rs 1321,
where you
can maintain a stoploss inside it if you want, so that if
you have to somehow lose clothes in the market
I have to stay away from the ups and
you are also taking the short term into account. If
you don't have any interest in the long term, then
you can put a stop loss on this function. The
long-term investors do
not care
because the future of the insurance company is
very bright. The kind of situation in which such
epidemic crises are increasing, in such a situation,
people are understanding the value of insurance
very well that
after any kind of problem, it can support you at the insurance level.
Now let us go about it. To
understand the pain here, ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Q4 net profit
rise was 23.3 Kunwar Officer. If we compare it with last year, it was
20%. Now we have
seen the results in the browser. Let us
try to understand a little more about the premium.
GTI, which is the red girlfriend, has
been 984 percent, which is the average industry
growth of 4.9 percent.
You can see in the comparison that if
we look at it, then there is a
growth of 22.61 percent in its profit, I have discussed it with you guys, let's see, till now the
profitability matrix of Combined Aishwarya is
1.01 percent, the
company rate is now from etc. What is this,
related to the body, their average
equity return policy, which is
1.8 percent from March 2018, and if
we compare it with the third quarter,
friend, and this is the same
quarter of 1.8 percent, and initially
if we compare it, then
you will
see that the accused is 21.7 percent, 20.8 percent
in Bachchan's computer,
Robin CDU, which is a
very important thing in the cases of insurance companies,
format e rickshaws, that is, the company's book
is so strong, and for this, IRDA has
made some norms and
solvent T in it.  The price of e-rickshaws should
be 1.50, which you are currently
seeing at 2.90. If you compare this point to
7.6 last year, it was
2.17. So, these are all gallery points in
which the solvency is looking strong in this show. The
company's run continues. The
premium income seems to be increasing, so the
result is also favorable. Now
I will also answer you that
why you have seen this loss figure in the operating profit.
You can see its revision here in
terms of witnesses, health claims, general
insurance and 98 looms
meaning of 2002. So, it is coming out to be an increase, with the
help of which you are getting to see this. So,
this stock was running at a very fast pace.
Due to the Kuwait situation, the
stock has fallen.
You and I know the value of insurance very well.
Other people will gradually
understand its importance. So,
whatever insurance says.  There is still a lot of growth left in Teacher India. In
such a situation, if
you are getting this offer at a lower level and you are
getting a discount coupon from your 52-week high,
then you
can gradually build a portion within it. But I will again tell you guys
that do not do any bulk buying
and never do any panic selling.
Make a graduation and gradually
if you want to exit from any insurance company or ease off, then
you should cool it
down gradually. In such a situation, one
important thing is that the insurance company
and the progress that you were seeing in such a good way,
if it comes down, then
this is an opportunity.
You should study about it, understand
its problems, try to understand it. If you have
any question or answer, you
can ask in the comment section.
I will try my best to explain it. This
video which I have
made in a very short way, I have not done the details,
so if you want to give details on it, its
script, then you can do it
in the comment section.  This is a method so that I
can share details antiseptic doubt on it 100% thanks for watching keep
investing stay safe thank you bye